A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Records of the Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 1996-2004., Extent: 29 boxes; 29 cubic feet. (Box 1-29)
  - Box 16.
    - Color Printers, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Conventional Wisdom, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Citigroup, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - CSPAN, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Charles E. Smith Realty, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - CTI Consultants, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
    - Important Addresses, 1996-2004 (Folder 42)
    - Crispin and Brenner PLLC, 1996-2004 (Folder 43)
    - CSL- Conventions, Sports and Leisure, 1996-2004 (Folder 44)
    - Covermaster, 1996-2004 (Folder 45)
    - New Copier Quotes, 1996-2004 (Folder 46)
    - Jane Coffey, 1996-2004 (Folder 47)
    - CSL John Kaatz, 1996-2004 (Folder 48)
    - Delaware North, 1996-2004 (Folder 49)
    - DSL Inquiries, 1996-2004 (Folder 50)
    - John Della Volpe, 1996-2004 (Folder 51)
    - Dun and Bradstreet, 1996-2004 (Folder 52)
    - Endorsements, 1996-2004 (Folder 53)
    - Eastern Realty, 1996-2004 (Folder 54)
    - Electronic Stapler, 1996-2004 (Folder 55)
    - ESPN: Peter Gammons, 1996-2004 (Folder 56)
    - George Mason University, 1996-2004 (Folder 57)
    - HNTB, 1996-2004 (Folder 58)
    - Delta Sky Miles, 1996-2004 (Folder 59)
    - Conventional Wisdom, 1996-2004 (Folder 60)
    - Dell, 2002 (Folder 61)
    - A.L. Eisenberg, 1996-2004 (Folder 62)
    - Ernst and Young, 1996-2004 (Folder 63)
    - Excel Courier Service, 1996-2004 (Folder 64)
    - Froehling and Robertson, Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 65)
    - Gardy McGrath International TV on the Web, 1996-2004 (Folder 66)
    - George Washington University Colonial Board, 1996-2004 (Folder 67)
    - George Washington University, 1996-2004 (Folder 68)
    - GWEC (Olympics), 1996-2004 (Folder 69)
    - GW Sports Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 70)
  - Box 17.
    - Fact Finding Stadium Visit Information: Visit Guests, Organizers, and Speakers, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Fact Finding: Guest Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Fact Finding: Questionnaire Summary, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Fact Finding: Survey Responses, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Expenses Fact Finding Stadium Visit, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Stadium Excursion Guests- Visits, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - MCI Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Football Stadium Tour, September 1998 (Folder 8)
    - MCI Arena Fact Finding Sheet, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Arlington, Texas: Ballpark at Arlington "Rangers", 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Cleveland: Jacobs Field, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Report of Visits, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Report of Visits with Photos, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - By-laws, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Meetings: Gabe's Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Documents, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Meeting Notes, 17 June 1999 (Folder 16)
    - Meeting Notes, 17 June 1999 (Folder 17)
    - CCPR and GL Subcommittee Meeting, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
  - Box 18.
    - Major League Baseball Presentation, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Submission to Major League Baseball, 2 September 2004 (Folder 2)
    - Suntrust, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Financing Plans, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Kagan, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - White and Baldacci, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Public Financial Management, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
  - Box 19.
    - National Football League: NFL vs. Oakland Raiders, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - National Football League: Lambeau Field, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - National Football League: Jack Kent Cooke Stadium, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - National Football League: Baltimore Ravens, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - National Football League: Philadelphia Eagles, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - National Football League: Minnesota Vikings, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - National Football League: San Diego Chargers, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - National Football League: Green Bay Packers vs. Professional Sports Marketing, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Urban Land Institute, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Cheryl Holzheimer Entzminger: Thesis- Mil. County Stadium, 1985 (Folder 10)
    - Citizens for Baseball in Wisconsin: Russel A. Hinz, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Ilitch Holdings, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - The Body Count, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Forbes Major League Baseball Valuations, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Architects, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Team Marketing Report, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Arlington Sites, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Arlington Site, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Arlington Zoning, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Fairfax Admissions Tax, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Fairfax County Zoning, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Kajima Urban Development, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Dulles World Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Costco Site, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - EPG Site, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Arlington Site Conference Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Arlington South Track, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Site Cafritz, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Debt Service, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Player Tax Issues, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - NOVA Growth, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - DC Area Percentage Tax Rates, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Virginia Census Data, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - DC Area's Highest Paid, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Attendance Projections, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Operating Assumptions, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Procurement, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - Duncan Hunter, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Blue Ribbon Panel, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Surveys, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - Stats, Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
    - Ballpark Operations Cost, 1996-2004 (Folder 42)
    - A/E Selection- Stadium, 1996-2004 (Folder 43)
  - Box 20.
    - Michael Schewel, Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, W. Tayloe Murphy, Jr., 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Transportation, Whittington Clement, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, Anita Rimler, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Technology, George C. Newstrom, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, John W. Marshall, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Secretary of Administration, Sandra D. Bowen, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Secretary of Education, Belle S. Wheelan, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Secretary of Finance, John M. Bennett, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Services, Jane Woods, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - Action Plans, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Delegate Bob Brink, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - DC Holdings/Capitol Hill, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Department of the Army, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - Lobbying Registration, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - Ron Tillett, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - Delegate C.A. Woodrum, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Legislative Information System, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Senator J.V. Gartlan, Jr., 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Senator Richard L. Saslaw, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Jim Moran, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Senator Herb Kohl, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Senator Mike DeWine, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - S. Vance Wilkins, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Senator George Allen, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Supervisor Dana Kuffman, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - State Purchasing, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - State of Virginia Risk Management, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Senator Charles S. Robb, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Majority Leader Dick Armey, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Honorable Dennis J. Kucinich, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Senator Russ Potts, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Joint Subcommittee Stadium Financing, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - Congressman Tom Davis, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Telephone Numbers House and Senate, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
    - Honorable John Hager, 1996-2004 (Folder 36)
    - Senator John Warner, 1996-2004 (Folder 37)
    - Senator Mary Margaret Whipple, 1996-2004 (Folder 38)
    - Senator Ticer, 1996-2004 (Folder 39)
    - Vance S. Wilkins, 1996-2004 (Folder 40)
    - Senator Janet D. Howell, 1996-2004 (Folder 41)
    - Commerce and Trade: Honorable Barry E. Duval, 1996-2004 (Folder 42)
    - Delegate Vince Callahan, 1996-2004 (Folder 43)
    - Senator John Warner, 1996-2004 (Folder 44)
    - G. Newstrom Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 45)
    - Todd Stottlemeyer, 1996-2004 (Folder 46)
    - Mark Warner, 1996-2004 (Folder 47)
    - Governor Warner, 1996-2004 (Folder 48)
    - Meetings- Governor, 1996-2004 (Folder 49)
    - Office of the Governor, 1996-2004 (Folder 50)
    - Robert Ehrlich- Maryland Governor, 1996-2004 (Folder 51)
    - Pictures, 1996-2004 (Folder 52)
    - Letters to Editors, 1996-2004 (Folder 53)
    - City of Alexandria, 1996-2004 (Folder 54)
    - Arlington County Board, 1996-2004 (Folder 55)
    - Arlington County Planning Commission, 1996-2004 (Folder 56)
    - Northern Virginia Delegation, 1996-2004 (Folder 57)
    - Biographies, 1996-2004 (Folder 58)
    - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1996-2004 (Folder 59)
    - Arlington County Civic Federation, 1996-2004 (Folder 60)
    - Arlington County Manager: Ron Clarke, 1996-2004 (Folder 61)
    - Charles Monroe: Arlington County Board, 1996-2004 (Folder 62)
    - Chamber Letters, 1996-2004 (Folder 63)
    - Alexandria City Council, 1996-2004 (Folder 64)
    - AZ Department of Commerce, 1996-2004 (Folder 65)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1996-2004 (Folder 66)
    - CATO Institute, 1996-2004 (Folder 67)
    - Department of Consumer Affairs, 1996-2004 (Folder 68)
    - Fairfax Bar Association, 1996-2004 (Folder 69)
    - Department of Tourism, 1996-2004 (Folder 70)
    - Greater Houston Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1996-2004 (Folder 71)
    - Herndon Chamber of Commerce, 1996-2004 (Folder 72)
    - Houston Sports Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 73)
    - Loudoun County Economic Development Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 74)
    - Laurel Hill Community Planning, 1996-2004 (Folder 75)
    - County of Loudoun Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 76)
    - Department of General Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 77)
    - Fairfax Government Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 78)
    - ICAR, 1996-2004 (Folder 79)
    - Mount Vernon- Lee Chamber, 1996-2004 (Folder 80)
    - Prince William County Board of Supervisors: Sean Connaughton, 1996-2004 (Folder 81)
    - National Jewish Medical Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 82)
    - National Association of Pro Baseball, 1996-2004 (Folder 83)
    - Loudoun County Board of Supervisors, 1996-2004 (Folder 84)
    - Fairfax County Federation of Citizens Association, 1996-2004 (Folder 85)
    - Stafford Economic Development Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 86)
    - National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, 1996-2004 (Folder 87)
    - Fairfax Government Center, 1996-2004 (Folder 88)
    - Oakton High School, 1996-2004 (Folder 89)
    - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, 1996-2004 (Folder 90)
    - Insurance OCIP, 1996-2004 (Folder 91)
    - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 92)
    - NOVA Regional Park Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 93)
    - Greater Washington Board of Trade, 1996-2004 (Folder 94)
    - Maryland Stadium Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 95)
    - Special License Plates, 1996-2004 (Folder 96)
    - Prince William County, 1996-2004 (Folder 97)
    - Washington Baseball Historical Society, 1996-2004 (Folder 98)
    - Fairfax County Council of PTAs, 1996-2004 (Folder 99)
    - Richmond Visitors Bureau, 1996-2004 (Folder 100)
    - Society for American Baseball Research, 1996-2004 (Folder 101)
    - NOVA Planning Community District, 1996-2004 (Folder 102)
    - Virginia Hospitality and Travel, 1996-2004 (Folder 103)
    - NOVA Transportation Alliance, 1996-2004 (Folder 104)
    - Phoenix Department of Finance, 1996-2004 (Folder 105)
    - Virginia Department of Planning and Budget, 1996-2004 (Folder 106)
    - Virginia Wine Wholesalers, 1996-2004 (Folder 107)
    - Virginia Local Government Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 108)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 109)
    - West Springfield Civic Association, 1996-2004 (Folder 110)
  - Box 21.
    - Financial Consultants, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Government Finance Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Contingent Liabilities: Contingent Liability Payment Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Contingent Liabilities: PHR and A (Tom Rust), 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - KPMG, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - KPMG: Peat Marwick, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - A and E RFP Docs, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - HOK Sport, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - David M. Schwarz Architectural Services, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - CDFM2, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
  - Box 22.
    - Hammes Co., 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - The Heartland Institute, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Jack W. Hill, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - H. Street Building Corporation, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Phil Hockberg, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Hurst Real Estate, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Hussey Seating Corporation, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Holland and Knight, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - International Facilities Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Imperial Parkings, 1996-2004 (Folder 10)
    - IAAM Information, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)
    - Jack Rouse Association, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Patrick Kane, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Key Bridge Marriott, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - KDR Real Estate Service, 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
    - The Leib Group: Bob Leib, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
    - LeClair Ryan, 1996-2004 (Folder 17)
    - Ron Labinski FAIA, 1996-2004 (Folder 18)
    - Joshua Lief, 1996-2004 (Folder 19)
    - Lincoln Properties, 1996-2004 (Folder 20)
    - Lehman Brothers, 1996-2004 (Folder 21)
    - Law Gibb Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 22)
    - Fred Malek, 1996-2004 (Folder 23)
    - Maps, 1996-2004 (Folder 24)
    - Midwest Express, 1996-2004 (Folder 25)
    - Martin Agency, 1996-2004 (Folder 26)
    - Manhattan, 1996-2004 (Folder 27)
    - Marsh Insurance, 1996-2004 (Folder 28)
    - Mills Corporation, 1996-2004 (Folder 29)
    - Metro Washington Airport Authority, 1996-2004 (Folder 30)
    - Metrorail, 1996-2004 (Folder 31)
    - Metro, 1996-2004 (Folder 32)
    - Mclean Hilton, 1996-2004 (Folder 33)
    - David Miller- IDEAs, 1996-2004 (Folder 34)
    - Monorail, 1996-2004 (Folder 35)
  - Box 23.
    - Site Selection, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Draft Report, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Proposal: HOK Sport, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - Proposal: CSC, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Proposal: HKS, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
  - Box 24.
    - Authority Minutes, 2002 (Folder 1)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Studies, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Minutes, Virginia Baseball Stadium Meetings, 2003 (Folder 3)
    - Community Communications, Public Relations and Government Liaison Committee Minutes, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Finance Minutes, 2002 (Folder 5)
    - [Untitled], 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Envelope, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Public Comment Sign In, 7 October, 2004 (Folder 8)
  - Box 25.
    - Audit, 200 (Folder 1)
    - Audit Annual Report, 2000 (Folder 2)
    - Audit Annual Report, 2001 (Folder 3)
    - Audit, 2002 (Folder 4)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Financial Statements, 1996 (Folder 5)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Financial Statements, 1997 (Folder 6)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Financial Statements, 1998 (Folder 7)
    - KPMG Audit, 1999 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Financial Statements, 1999 (Folder 9)
  - Box 26.
    - Report: "Impact of a New Major League Baseball Team in Northern Virginia on the Baltimore Orioles". Goal Group Consulting, LLS; Kagan Media Appraisals, Inc; Penn, Schoen and Berland Associates, Inc., 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Stadium Managers Association Seminar, 2003 (Folder 2)
    - Occoquan Site Analysis, 1996-2004 (Folder 3)
    - IDEA (Information Display and Entertainment Association) Membership Directory, 2003 (Folder 4)
    - Reports: Ballpark Financing Scenario 1: Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority Stand-Alone Projections, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Reports: Ballpark Financing Scenario 2: Third-Party Developer Participation Projection, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Catalogs: Goldstar Embroidery, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Time Global Business Report: The Other Washington, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Ballpark Financing Plan: MZ Sports, LLC., 19 May 2004 (Folder 9)
    - Ballpark Financing Plan: MZ Sports, LLC., 20 August 2004 (Folder 10)
    - Ballpark Financing Plan: MC Sports, LLC., 10 July 2003 (Folder 11)
    - Appraisal Report: Dulles World Center, 2 June 2004 (Folder 12)
    - "Comprehensive Growth Trends in the Greater Washington/Northern Virginia Region. 1970-2000-2030", Stephen S. Fuller. George Mason University, March 2003 (Folder 13)
    - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority: Ballpark Development in the 1990s. PFM, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - "Economic and Fiscal Impacts of a Major League Baseball Franchise and Stadium in the Commonwealth of Virginia", 1996-2004 (Folder 15)
  - Box 27.
    - Occoquan Site Analysis, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Arlington Site, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Major League Baseball Issues. ZH., October 2003 (Folder 3)
    - Baseball Stadium Site Analysis, Arlington County, Virginia, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - 2 Calendars, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
  - Box 28.
    - Public Opinion Study: John Della Vopa, 1996-2004 (Folder 1)
    - Contracts VBC, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - House Document #7, 1997 (Folder 3)
    - Directions, 1996-2004 (Folder 4)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Lease Negotiations, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Metrocall, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Larry Trollinger, 1996-2004 (Folder 7)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Mike Scanlon Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Bill Collins Biography, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Agreement, 2004 (Folder 10)
    - Virginia Baseball Club Extension, 27 August 2003 (Folder 11)
    - Virginia Baseball Club Payment History, 1996-2004 (Folder 12)
    - Virginia Baseball Club: Jim Speros, 1996-2004 (Folder 13)
    - Virginia Baseball Club Committee Assignments, 1996-2004 (Folder 14)
    - New Agreement, Virginia Baseball Club, 2002 (Folder 15)
    - Wachovia, 1996-2004 (Folder 16)
  - Box 29.
    - Purchase Orders, 2001-2002 (Folder 1)
    - Credit Cards- Visa, 1996-2004 (Folder 2)
    - Visa Paid, 2001 (Folder 3)
    - Gretchen Hamm, 2002 (Folder 4)
    - Envision, 1996-2004 (Folder 5)
    - Office Policies, 1996-2004 (Folder 6)
    - Visa Paid, 2000 (Folder 7)
    - Dell Computer Equipment, 1996-2004 (Folder 8)
    - Operating Budget, 1996-2004 (Folder 9)
    - Financial Statements, 1998 (Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Correspondence, 1996-2004 (Folder 11)